A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office of Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006
Library of Virginia
- III. Legislative Files, 2002-2005 (accession 42414)., Extent: 47.95 cubic feet (137 boxes). (Box 38-174)
  - 2004 Session
    - House of Delegates
      - HB 1444 (04) Humelsine Parkway; Designating as Route 199 between I-64 East and West of Williamsburg City (Box 121, Folder 5)
      - HB 1445 (04) School Crossing Guards; Use of Hand-Held Stop Signs to Control Traffic (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1447 (04) Department of Accounts to Conduct Recovery Audits of State Contracts (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1448 (04) Wine and Beer Shippers; Fees for Licenses (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1450 (04) Petroleum Storage Tank Fund; Reimbursements (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1452 (04) Fresh Water and Saltwater Fishing; a Combined License May Be Established (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1453 (04) Real Estate Tax; Collection Proceedings for Delinquent Taxes (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1456 (04) Nuisances; Abatement, Sale of Property for Delinquent Taxes (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1460 (04) Judgment and Legal Rate of Interest; Lowered (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1461 (04) Real Estate Assessments; Establishment of Dept. in Powhatan County (Box 121, Folder 6)
      - HB 1463 (04) RS and UT; Constitutional Nexus for Imposition (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - HB 1474 (04) Stuart Finley Bridge; Designated as Bridge on Potterton Drive over Lake Barcroft in Fairfax County (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - HB 1475 (04) Vietnamese-American Heritage Flag; Recognition (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - HB 1480 (04) Virginia-Asian Advisory Board; Purpose (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - HB 1483 (04) Communicable Diseases of Public Health Threat; Procedure for Quarantine and Isolation (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - HB 1485 (04) Liability Insurance for Localities; Adds Fire and Police Dept. Operational Medical Directors and Physicians, Directors (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - HB 1486 (04) State Income Tax; Limiting Legislation Creating Voluntary Contribution of Refunds to Charitable Organizations (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - HB 1489 (04) Banquet and Mixed Beverage Licenses; Issuance (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Senate
      - SB 1 (04) Out-of-Family Investigations Advisory Committee; Membership (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 2 (04) State Publications; Reduces Number Submitted to State Library (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 3 (04) Special Funds; Abolishes those that are Dormant and their Associated Programs (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 4 (04) Housing Funds; Changes in Utilization Reporting Requirements (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 5 (04) Medical Complaint Investigation Committees and Medical and Psychological Practices Audit Committee; Abolished (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 6 (04) State Agency Reports; Changes in Distribution of Annual and Biennial Copies (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 7 (04) Collegial Body; Definition (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 8 (04) Interagency Coordinating Council on Housing for Disabled; Abolished (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 9 (04) VEC; Eliminates Requirement for Development of a Workforce Plan (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - SB 10 (04) Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations; Abolished (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 11 (04) State Agencies; Eliminates Requirement to Report on Costs of Federal Mandates (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 12 (04) Recycling Markets Development Council; Duties (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 13 (04) Sam Snead Memorial Highway; Designing Route 220 in Bath (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 14 (04) Utility Tax; Imposition on Local Consumers in Town of Iron Gate for Mobile Phone Usage (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 18 (04) Constitutional Amendment; Effective Dates of Legislative and Congressional Redistricting (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 19 (04) Guardians of Incapacitated Persons; Prohibits Change in Martial Status without prior Court Approval (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 21 (04) Special License Plates; Issuance to Various Organizations (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 24 (04) Interpreters for Non-English Speaking Persons in Mental Commitment Proceedings; Provisions (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 25 (04) Temporary Detention Orders; Technical Correction to Cross Reference (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - SB 26 (04) Littering; Offense for Which Use of Summons May Be Issued in Juvenile Court (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 31 (04) Higher Educational Institutions Bond Bill of 2004 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 32 (04) Parking Facilities Bond Bill of 2004 (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 34 (04) Jack and Carter Hardesty Bridge; Designating as Route 340 Bridge in Clark County (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 35 (04) Guardianship of Children; Subsidy for Relative Caregivers (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 38 (04) Jury Service; Exempts Certain Legislative Employees (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 39 (04) Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS); Financing Through Bonds (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 44 (04) Health Insurance; Coverage for Biologically Based Mental Illness (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 45 (04) State and Local Health Departments; Chesterfield County May Supplement Salaries and Expenses of Employees (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - SB 50 (04) Advisory Board on Child Abuse and Neglect; Duties (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 51 (04) Divorce; Property Distribution (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 54 (04) Waterfowl, Migratory and Non-Migratory; Allows Certain Localities to Prohibit Feeding, Penalty (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 57 (04) Richmond Metropolitan Authority; Free Use of Toll Facilities by Quadriplegics (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 58 (04) Signs; Maintenance and Repair of Non-Conforming Signs by Transportation Commissioner (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 61 (04) Regional Emergency Medical Services Councils; Exempt from Consumer Affairs Regulatory Requirements (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 62 (04) Adoption; Requirements for Agencies Outside State (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 69 (04) Buchanan County Tourist Train Development Authority (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 71 (04) Local Consumer Utility Tax; Exemption for Churches (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - SB 72 (04) Roadway Litter Pick-Up; Civil Immunity of Officials who Participate in Programs for Probationers (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 73 (04) Churches; Recordation Taxes on Incorporated Churches or Religious Bodies (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 76 (04) Campaign Signs; Regulations (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 78 (04) Kinship Care; Definition (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 81 (04) Neighborhood Assistance Act; Tax Credit for Donations of Professional Services (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 86 (04) Medical Care Facilities COPN; Criteria for Determining Need (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 90 (04) Criminal History Records Check; Locality May Require Applicant or Licensee to Pay Cost of Fingerprinting (Box 123, Folder 1)
      - SB 94 (04) Polling Places; Voting Equipment Must Remain in Plain View of Officers of Election (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 95 (04) Public Procurement Act; Includes On-line Auctions and U.S. General Services Administration (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 97 (04) Charter; City of Fairfax (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 98 (04) Parenting Programs; Created within Department of Correctional Education (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 99 (04) Concealed Weapons; Exempts Certain Retired Law-Enforcement Officers from Permit Fees (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 101 (04) Pedestrians; Installation and Maintenance of Signs Requiring Motorists to Yield Right-of-Way in Loudoun County (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 103 (04) Child Custody and Visitation; Filing Fee for Appeals (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 107 (04) Toll Facilities; Allows Operator or Toll Collection Technician to Obtain Vehicle Owner Information from DMV (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 110 (04) Water Supply Plan Regulations; Effective Date (Box 123, Folder 2)
      - SB 112 (04) Franchised Motorcycle Dealers; Repurchase of Motorcycles, Parts and Equipment by Manufacturers (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 114 (04) Abandoned Children; Protection, Affirmative Defense to Prosecution of Parent (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 115 (04) Automobile Graveyards and Junkyards; Screening Requirements in Certain Counties (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 118 (04) Pleadings; Notice to Agent on Amendment (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 119 (04) Uniform Commercial Code; Revisions Concerning Electronic Documents of Title (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 120 (04) Public Service Corporations; Filing of Annual Report (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 122 (04) Real Estate Tax; Allows Goochland County to Increase Amount of Income for Elderly or Disabled (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 124 (04) Charter; City of Richmond (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - SB 125 (04) Water Wells; Location and Testing in Goochland County (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 126 (04) Virginia-North Carolina Interstate High-Speed Rail Compact (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 127 (04) Farm Vehicles; Registration Fees for Plant Nurseries and Christmas Tree Farms (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 130 (04) Unemployment Compensation; Penalties for Late Filing (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 131 (04) Corporations; Articles of Termination of Corporate Existence (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 136 (04) Health Records; Release of Patient Information to Commissioner of Department of Labor and Industry Due to Death, etc. (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 139 (04) High-Occupancy Toll (HOT) Lanes; VDOT when Making Improvements to I-66 to Include (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 145 (04) Teachers; Procedure for Licensure and Suspension and Revocation of Licenses (Box 123, Folder 4)
      - SB 148 (04) Toll Facilities; Disclosure of Data Generated by Automated Electronic Toll-Collection Systems (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 149 (04) FOIA; Exempts Certain Client Lists of Persons Receiving Transportation Services (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 150 (04) Sheep Board; Composition (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 152 (04) Industrial Development Authorities; Any Locality Authorized to Refer thereto as an Economic Development Authority (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 153 (04) Roanoke Higher Education Authority; Board of Trustees (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 154 (04) Fire Programs Fund; Use (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 155 (04) George Fortune, Jr. Memorial Bridges; Designating as I-66 Bridge over Route 29 in Fairfax County (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 156 (04) Dental Plan Organizations; Provisions (Box 123, Folder 5)
      - SB 158 (04) Pharmaceutical Information; Dissemination of Medicare Benefits and Training of Senior Citizen Volunteers (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 159 (04) Athletic Trainers; Licensure (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 160 (04) Physician-Patient Relationships; Effect of Certain Emergency Department Treatment (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 161 (04) Computers; Disposition of Surplus Equipment (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 162 (04) Magistrates; Abolishes Training Requirements by Commonwealth Attorneys (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 163 (04) SCC Bureau of Financial Institutions; Submission of Confidential Information Pursuant to Grand Jury (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 165 (04) Tax Information; Release to Help Facilitate Collection of Unpaid Wages (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 166 (04) Tax Information; Release to Aid in Locating Holders of Unclaimed Property (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - SB 167 (04) Racing Commission; Authorized to Increase Number of Satellite Facilities (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 171 (04) Wireless E-911 Fund; Provisions for Payments (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 172 (04) Appeals Bonds; Ceiling (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 173 (04) Higher Educational Institutions; Definition Includes a Governmental Instrumentality (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 174 (04) Judicial Retirement System; Maximum Credit a Former Judge may Transfer (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 177 (04) Capital Cases; Appointment of Counsel (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 179 (04) Unemployment Compensation; Benefit Charges Resulting form a Temporary Work Closure Forced by Disaster (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 181 (04) Assisted Living Facilities; Regulations for Emergency Electrical Systems (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 183 (04) Building Code; Standards for Fire Detection and Suppression Systems in Nursing Homes and Facilities (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 184 (04) Senatorial Districts; Changes in Boundaries in Chesapeake (Box 124, Folder 1)
      - SB 185 (04) Child Abuse or Neglect; Includes Childhelp USA in List of Volunteer Organizations Subject to Search of Central Registry (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 186 (04) Virginia-Asian Advisory Board; Purpose (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 190 (04) Water and Sewage Systems; Mandatory Connection in Wythe County (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 194 (04) Unemployment Compensation; Allowed Two Weeks of Benefits if Terminated before Resignation Date (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 197 (04) Medical Care Facilities COPN; Not Applicable to Certain Intermediate Care Facilities for Mentally Retarded (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 199 (04) Damage Stamp Program; Extends Coverage to Beekeepers (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 200 (04) Beekeeper Assistance Program (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 201 (04) Grievance Procedures; Revision of State Guidelines (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 202 (04) DUI; Procedure Due to Refusal to Submit to Breath or Blood Testing (Box 124, Folder 2)
      - SB 203 (04) Charter; City of Falls Church (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - SB 204 (04) Inoperable Motor Vehicles; to be Shielded or Screened from View (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - SB 206 (04) Annexation; Moratorium on City and County Immunity Notices and Proceedings (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - SB 208 (04) Child Support; Guidelines Not to Include Calculation of Income from 2nd Job, Payment of Medical Expenses (Box 124, Folder 3)
      - SB 211 (04) Charter; City of Franklin (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 212 (04) Inspector General for Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse; Duties (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 214 (04) Courthouse and Courtroom Security; Assessment Fee (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 215 (04) Voter Registrars; Appointment, Term and Removal (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 223 (04) Adoption, Marriage and Divorce Records; Deletes Statements Indicating Racial Designations (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 224 (04) Medical Treatment Options; Physician Disclosure (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 226 (04) State and Local Government Conflict of Interests Act; Orientation Programs for State Government Personnel (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 227 (04) Firearms; Permit to Sell or Purchase in Certain Counties (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 228 (04) Land Use Proceedings; Disclosures (Box 124, Folder 4)
      - SB 230 (04) Brown v. Board of Education Scholarship Program and Fund (Box 124, Folder 5)
      - SB 231 (04) Corporate Income Tax; Reduces New Emp. Threshold to Rec. Major Business Facility Job Tax Credit (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 233 (04) Housing Authorities; Development of a "No Trespass" Policy (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 234 (04) Claims; Julius Earl Ruffin (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 236 (04) Domestic Violence, Sexual Assault, Stalking and Violation of Protective Order; Training of Personnel to Handle (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 241 (04) Land Records; Use of Secure Remote Access, Increases Technology Trust Fund Fee (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 242 (04) Post-Disaster Anti-Price Gouging Act; Created (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 244 (04) Community College Boards and Boards of Visitors; Appointment of Faculty Representatives (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 246 (04) Signs; Posting in Certain Areas Where Yard Signs, Auctions, etc., are Being Held (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 252 (04) Bicycles, Mopeds, Etc.; Restrictions on Use on Roadways (Box 124, Folder 6)
      - SB 257 (04) Subdivision Streets; Taking Into Secondary Highway System (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 259 (04) Special License Plates; Issuance to Hobbyists of Reconstructed, Restored, etc., Vehicles (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 260 (04) Comprehensive Roadside Management Program; Established within the Department of Transportation (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 261 (04) Wildlife; Prohibits Use of Drugs Thereon (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 262 (04) Milk Commission; Continued within the Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 266 (04) Medical Assistance Services; Includes Long-Term Care Partnership Program (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 267 (04) Rivanna River Basin Commission, Created (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 270 (04) Homeless Children; Public School Enrollment (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 271 (04) Felony Conviction; Compensation for Wrongful Incarceration (Box 125, Folder 1)
      - SB 273 (04) Commercial Vehicles; Parking Regulations in Towns in Fairfax County (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 274 (04) Marriage Rites; Persons Who May Perform (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 276 (04) Assault and Battery; Reporting of Spousal Abuse by Active Members of Armed Forces (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 277 (04) Transportation Projects; VDOT to Maintain Property Acquired for (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 278 (04) Telemedicine Initiatives; Abolishes Reporting Requirements by Commissioner of Health (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 280 (04) Cable Television Services by Certain Localities; Provisions (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 283 (04) University of Virginia's College at Wise; Reduced Tuition (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 285 (04) Licensure by Board of Contractors; DPOR and Board to Establish Program (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 286 (04) Ballots; Names Printed only for One Office, Exception (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 288 (04) Driver Training Schools; Regulation by DMV (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 289 (04) State Property Management; Division of Engineering and Buildings to Establish Performance Standard to Determine Effect (Box 125, Folder 2)
      - SB 297 (04) FOIA; Exempts Numbers for Cell Phones, Pagers, etc., of Law-Enforcement Personnel (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 298 (04) Conservators of the Peace; Includes Special Agents of Department of Homeland Security (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 302 (04) Public Procurement Act; Cooperative Procurement with U.S. General Services Administration (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 303 (04) Cemeteries; Authorization for Interment (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 304 (04) State Agencies in Executive Branch; to Identify Drug Treatment and Job Training Programs they Administer (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 308 (04) Community Criminal Justice Boards; Representation at Meetings (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 310 (04) Wine Board and Wine Promotion Fund; Created, Abolishes Winegrowers Advisory Board (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 311 (04) Law Officers' Retirement System; Retirement Benefits of Persons in a Hazardous Position (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 313 (04) Election Laws; Changes in Voter Equipment and Technology (Box 125, Folder 3)
      - SB 315 (04) Green Schools Program; to Promote Waste Reduction and Resource Efficiency (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - SB 316 (04) Utility Tax; Imposition on Local Consumers in Towns of Herndon and Vienna for Mobile Phone Usage (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - SB 317 (04) Missing Children; Increases Age Allowed for Reporting, Information Entered into Criminal Information Network (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - SB 318 (04) Adult Protective Services; Change in Provisions, Commissioner of DSS to Report on Adult Abuse, etc. (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - SB 319 (04) Feticide; Penalty (Box 125, Folder 4)
      - SB 320 (04) Racketeering Influenced and Corrupt Organization (RICO) Act; Created (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 321 (04) Gangs; Definition, Penalty Upon Conviction of Criminal Activity; Forfeiture of Property, etc. (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 323 (04) Workers' Compensation; Deposit to be Made by Self-Insurers in Order to Secure Payment for Liability (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 324 (04) Motor Vehicle Purchases; Cure Offers for Consumer Disputes (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 325 (04) Counterfeit Controlled Substance; Definition (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 326 (04) Concealed Weapons; Applicability while Engaged in Hunting (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 327 (04) Committee on District Courts; Chief Justice a Member and Chairman (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 328 (04) Judges; Notice of Retirement (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 329 (04) Driver's License; Driving After Forfeiture for DUI Conviction, Penalty (Box 125, Folder 5)
      - SB 330 (04) Public Defender Commission; Name Changed to Indigent Defense Commission (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - SB 333 (04) Felony Convictions; Issuance of Writ of Actual Innocence for Non-Biological Evidence (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - SB 334 (04) Bail Enforcement Agents; Regulation and Licensure (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - SB 335 (04) Child Custody or Visitation; Service of Summons on Teacher, etc., for Attendance and Testimony (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - SB 336 (04) JIRC; Removes Confidentiality of Evidence Concerning a Judge (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - SB 337 (04) Health Records; Privacy, Access, etc. (Box 125, Folder 6)
      - SB 338 (04) Higher Education Institutions; Duties Include Facilitate Development of Articulation Agreement Between 2 and 4 Year Institutions (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 341 (04) Concealed Weapons; Reciprocity Agreements for Law Enforcement Officers (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 343 (04) Fraud Against Taxpayers Act; Not Applicable to Claims, Records or Statements Relating to State and Local Taxes (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 344 (04) Telephone Privacy Protection Act; Prohibits Telephone Solicitation to Persons on Do-Not-Call Registry (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 345 (04) Commercial Driver's License; Imposition of Additional Fees for Hazmat Endorsements (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 347 (04) RS and UT; Extends Sunset Provisions for Textbooks for Free Distribution to Professors (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 348 (04) Property Owners' Association Act; Access to Committee and Subcommittee Meetings of Board of Directors (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 349 (04) Personal Property Exempt from Taxation; Including Vehicles Owned by Volunteer Rescue and Fire Organizations (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 350 (04) Motor Vehicle License Decals; Free Issuance to Volunteer Fire Department and Rescue Squad Members (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 352 (04) FOIA; Reorganization of Record Exemptions (Box 126, Folder 1)
      - SB 353 (04) Transportation Infrastructure; Provisions in Comprehensive Plan (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 354 (04) FOIA; Exempts Records of Sexually Violent Predator Commitment Review Committee (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 355 (04) Insurance; Domestic Reciprocals (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 359 (04) Referenda; Local Distribution of Information (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 361 (04) Real Estate Tax; Allows Northern Virginia Increase Amount of Income for Elderly or Disabled (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 362 (04) Disabled Parking License Plates and Placards; Issuance to Parents and Legal Guardians of Persons with Disabilities (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 363 (04) Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers Board and Migrant Worker Policy Committee; Under Auspices of VEC (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 364 (04) Design-Build Contracts; Use by Director of Department of Rail and Public Transportation (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 365 (04) Environmental Permit Fees; Applicable to Water and Non-Hazardous Solid Waste (Box 126, Folder 2)
      - SB 366 (04) Public Service Corporations; Locality to Determine Taxation of Real and Tangible Personal Property (Box 126, Folder 3)
      - SB 369 (04) Public Utilities; Mutual Aid Agreements Between Localities (Box 126, Folder 3)